http://www.risingup.com/privacy_policy.html

Contact|RisingUp HomeHomeAircraft SpecsAviation Message BoardFAA RegulationsAircraft PicturesAvation LinksPractice FAA TestsPrivacy PolicyUser AgreementRisingUp HomePrivacy PolicyHome > Privacy Policy
RisingUp.com takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it.
Routine Information Collection
All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.
Cookies and Web Beacons
Where necessary, RisingUp.com uses cookies to store information about a visitor's preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and present the visitor with customized content.
Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.
3rd Party Advertisers
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
More Information
Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.
Contact Information
Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to webmaster@risingup.com for further clarification.
NavigationPrivacy PolicyUser AgreementRisingUp HomeUse of this website constitutes acceptance of our Privacy Policy and User Agreement.Copyright © 1998-2011 RisingUp Aviation. All rights reserved.
